LAUREN R. MOORE

Cincinnati, Ohio 45224 ◆ 215-292-4656 ◆ Imooreintech2021@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Committed team player - seeks technical role. Engaging interpersonal skill and experience. Experience in Agile-SCRUM method, (SDLC), ITIL v.3 and v.4 Service Management frameworks. Endeavoring to deliver value, and continue to grow in service of a great mission.

SKILLS

- Certified Internet Web Professional (June 2021)
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Agile-Scrum Methodology
- SDLC Process

- ITIL v. 3 & v.4 Service Management
- Technical Business Analyst user story author
- Team and individual contributor

Work History

Housekeeper, 04/2020 to 10/2020

Crothall Health Care: Client: Children's Hospital – Cincinnati, Ohio

Cleaned and sanitized inpatient rooms and ancillary areas as assigned

Earned 100% sanitation score from visiting RN infection preventionist

Used Epic software to track Discharge cleans and room changes

Used Walter Biometric software system to track hours worked

Awarded July's GEM Award by facility director for cleaning excellence

Voted 'Employee of the Month' for July 2020

Awarded an e-card by PB3.200 unit for teaching children cleaning skills

IT Team Member, 06/2016 to 06/2018

Thrive Impact Sourcing – Cincinnati, Ohio

- Authored and conducted on-boarding training and presentations to train (6) new analysts and (2) Huddle Leads over 6 months for both Thrive and Caresource team
- Launched and presided over ThriveCares community outreach committee doubling its active membership in 2017 from 6 to 12
- Organized and supported Thrive volunteer events for 2016-2018 supporting 93% volunteerism rate for 2017
- Upheld and Heralded Thrive/Ingage Partners as coveted B-Corp organizations

Technical Business Analyst, 07/2017 to 04/2018

Client: Caresource – Dayton, Ohio

- Conducting many interviews to elicit requirements from stakeholders, team members, State representatives and vendors
- Formulating hundreds of technical, complex-scenario Acceptance criteria that captures required Business conditions to correct problematic issues internal and external to Caresource
- Favorably impacting medically frail, impoverished populations, regulatory standards, precluding organizational fines, sanctions, corrective action plans in Ohio, Kentucky, Indiana, Georgia and West Virginia
- Enhancing claims processing and data exchange processes including Medicare and Medicaid regulatory guidelines
- Liaison for Claims team and requestors to ensure quality for user stories
- Generating hundreds of User Stories using Triage ticket information that included: Business features, Lines of Business (LOB's), Market States and all pertinent detail listed.
- Facilitated subscriber reporting and issue- for strategic resolution to critical departments within company

Software Quality Analyst, 07/2016 to 07/2017

Client: Caresource – Dayton, Ohio

- Performed Multi-environment testing: Integration, Certification, Regression testing observing quality standards to create lasting, quality changes for members/requestors during production stage
- Mocked complex scenario test data to mimic acceptance criteria scenarios of user stories
- Created Test Cases placing them in team repository for trace-ability
- Consulted each week with Product Owner re: User Story backlog and pain-points
- Presented test results to Stakeholder/Business in User Acceptance meetings
- Participated in Agile/Scrum ceremonies (Daily Standup, Grooming, Retrospective, Sprint Planning)

STNA Contractor/Private Duty Aide, 04/2006 to 04/2016

Self – Cincinnati, OH

- Provided patient care in hospitals, nursing homes, hospice facilities
- Provided meal prep, housekeeping, shopping, errands, companionship
- Documented and submitted 100% services rendered for agency patients
- Traveled to (2) foreign and (9) domestic locations with clients as needed
- Reported emergency events to first responders and management
- Provided therapeutic conversation for those distressed re: their condition
- Prepared weekly progress reports to families re: client condition sent via email

Family Services Assistant, 05/2003 to 08/2003

Cincinnati Public Schools - Cincinnati, Ohio

Assisted parents enroll their children in the Head Start program

Referred medical experts to parents for special needs testing

Coordinated Parent Education forums and workshops for growth & learning

Engaged with parents, teachers and children in a warm professional manner

Documented services provided and submitted them in a timely manner Communicated with CPS on the status of each child in the assigned schools

Eligibility Technician, 01/2002 to 05/2003

Hamilton County Jobs And Family Services - Cincinnati, Ohio

- Interviewed applicants and explained scope of different available benefits.
- Documented all communication with applicants and inputted information into system using in-house computer systems.
- Scheduled appointments with applicants to gather information and explain benefits processes.
- Communicated with people from various cultures and backgrounds on application process.
- Educated patients on eligibility and affordability options by offering insightful information.

State Tested Nursing Assistant, 09/1992 to 06/1994

Mother Margaret Hall – Cincinnati, Ohio

- Helped patients effectively manage routine bathing, grooming, oral hygiene
- Delivered individualized patient care by recording vital signs and documenting observations
- Obtained biological specimens for ordered tests and prepared for laboratory transport.
- Complied with all company-specific guidelines and performed hands-on nursing care to patients under RN supervision.
- Cared for clients with diagnoses such as Alzheimer's, respiratory failure, diabetes, Parkinson's disease etc.
- Participated in Bingo, arts and craft activities with patients to boost mood, improve overall memory and provide light entertainment.

EDUCATION -

Web Development, Expected in 06/2021

Kable Academy - Cincinnati, OH

ITIL/ServiceNow Administration, 12/2020

Per Scholas - Cincinnati. Ohio

Software Quality Testing, 06/2016

Per Scholas - Cincinnati, OH

Business Analyst Requirement Solicitation, 09/2017

MAX Training - Cincinnati, OH

Technical Business Analyst Workshop Training: 10/2017

Client- Sponsored Training - Cincinnati, OH

Bachelor of Arts

Mount St. Joseph University - Cincinnati, OH

CERTIFICATIONS
ITIL v.3 Service Management Framework (2021)
State of Ohio Department of Insurance - Life Insurance Producer (2019)
International Software Testing Qualifications Board(ISTQB) - Foundations Level (2017)

Kable Academy

Per Scholas

B.I.T.

Agile Cincinnati

Women Who Code

Ohio Life Insurance Producers (agent)

Dress for Success - Professional Women's Group

International Institute of Business Analysis (IIBA)